A'MR DAWOODI

 $Syria\ Damascus\ |\ (099)\ 959-6071\ |\ \underline{amr.dawoodi@hotmail.com}\ |\ \underline{www.linkedin.com/in/omar-dawoodi-65044b201/}$

Summary

information technology graduates with 3 years' software developer experience, I can control my time very well, handling my customer needs in satisfactorily way for both sides.

Managing the team and the work mechanism to reach the best results in projects by coordinating cooperation and the ability to distribute tasks with high performance.

EDUCATION

Professional Baccalaureate Degree (information technology

JUN 2018

Damascus • School

Graduated from Syrian Virtual University

MAR 2024

branch Bachelor in Information Technology (BAIT) Specialization Information Systems and Data networks (ISDN)

Master of Web Science (M.Sc. in Web Science).

AUG 2024

The master of Web Science (MWS) program is suitable for all IT

SKILLS

- Full-stack developer
- IT HELP DESK
- Network administration
- Sales strategy
- social media Marketing

- SQL Server
- Design
- Information security
- Webmaster tools
- Google analytics

WORK EXPERIENCE

Website and Application Development – freelance

Website Blogger and Sales Manager -freelance

JUNE 2019 - JAN 2020

• Website Blogger and Sales Manager for laptops

IT Help Desk • Al Hadara

FEB 2020 - NOV 2021

• My responsibility:

helping employers to problem-solving process.

Record events and problems and their resolution in logs.

Provide information on IT products or services.

describe the best solution based on the issue and details provided by customers.

remote troubleshooting through diagnostic techniques and pertinent questions.

finding and solve complex problems

Programmer / Network Manager • Aya

MAR 2022 - AUG 2023

• My responsibility:

Upgrading, repair, and maintain computer networks.

Managing clouding and physical network storage.

Deploy and update company-wide software.

managing the company network

Web Developer Full Stack • Rexos

JUN 2023 – MAR 2024

It Manager – Full Stack Developer as A Team Leader. we have completed a full project, the system was "Web Application" with Blazor framework and Asp.Net, the system was for automation gas stations to full control and process happens in stations and processing all information and store it, values are taken from sensors connected with system by serials ports.

with a lot of features...

my responsibilities front-end with back-end shared with my two partners

Windows Application Full Stack • JoyBox

Feb 2024 – Set 2024

• Development of a complete pharmacy management and accounting program. The Shiva Pharmacy program was developed individually, knowing that the work on it was not from scratch. The project was successfully delivered, ensuring its operation within pharmacies and the experiment.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Professional Microsoft office.
- virtual studio C# / virtual studio code.
- Tools: Git & GitHub, VC, PRD.
- High experience with Linux, Ubuntu OS, system security.
- cyber security ethical hacking 60% knowledge.
- High expert as an IT help Desk / solving problem.
- Strong knowledge of computer maintenance.
- Experience in the field of networking (cable stapling introducing
- Experienced in utilizing ERP systems for managing core business processes, including data entry, reporting, and supporting users, with a focus on improving workflow efficiency.
- computers to the domain defining printers Finger Print).
- Experience Laravel 8 months.

- Web Developer (HTML +5, CSS, JavaScript, React, Sass, PHP, WordPress, Next JS, Tailwind)
- Dealing with API's
- Blazer framework, I have a project Full blazer
- Adobe Photoshop 70%/ instructor 40%.
- Microsoft SQI server and dealing with virtual servers.
- Drowlo Building ERD plans.
- Oracle 19 Database.

PORTFOLIO

• https://amr-dawoodi-portfolio.vercel.app/